I could wear it.
You can have as many as you want.
Such a cute dress...
Ta-da!
It's shwashy!
Delicious!
Hello everyone, I'm Hinano Kamimura of Hinatazaka46. Today I'm here on the Hinatazaka Channel to search for Showa-retro items.
I've always loved the Showa-era retro atmosphere and items, so today I'd like to borrow this opportunity to go on an exciting journey with the Hinatazaka Channel.
So today, I'd like to take this opportunity to take you on a journey of my own excitement.
It's a wonderful shopping arcade with a retro atmosphere.
It's still at the entrance, but it's already nice.
It's so nice!
Look at this.
Morning glories
Like this.
It's nice... a normal stroll...
There are so many stores!
Hi, I'm Hinano.
I think I found the store you're looking for here.
Here it is!
I found the store I was looking for, Harmony General Store.
I've come to an amazing store!
I'm so excited!
Let's go in!
Wow, it's so nice!
It smells so good!
We've come to a wonderful store!
It looks like they have retro Showa-era goods.
I'm kind of longing for it!
The store is like a secret base filled with skis.
I'm hoping to find and get my favorite item here today.
I'd like to get it and go home!
It's so nice... what should I do?
What should I wear?
So cute!
I tend to pick up blue clothes easily.
I often go to thrift stores.
I usually choose blue at first.
But I think that red and other yellowish colors suit me best.
It's a bit difficult to find clothes that suit me and that I like.
It's cute, but today's theme is Showa-era retro.
Cute! Very retro!
Cute!
I think the shoulders are a little wide.
But the shape also has a Showa-era feel to it, so it's really cute.
I don't know...
What's wrong with Hinano Kamimura?
She's a bit indecisive.
So I'm not sure if she can make up her mind.
She's already looking at them one by one.
Cute checks like this...
Cute!
The collar is cute.
The collar is so cute.
I'd buy it!
I really can't choose one. There are a lot of one-piece dresses on the top.
I love it!
This one!
What is this?
What is this? By the way...
It's a water bottle.
A water bottle? It's cute.
Just put it on.
It's so cute.
May I?
I just think it's so cute.
Thank you very much.
Look at this water bottle.
Do you think I'll use it? But it's so cute just hanging it up.
I want to put it on today.
Keep it.
May I?
Keep.
Excuse me, please.
Just a minute, please.
There are so many great products, it's hard to decide.
That's all I'm saying.
This one's cute.
This is cute!
I want to buy this one, no questions asked!
Why? Because they are psyllium colors!
Red and green
This is my crush point!
Look at this... crush point...
Look at this button.
I know, I have a crush on this button.
I'll buy this one.
Wow, this one is cute too!
I wish there was a waist-marking belt or something for this, too.
It's also important that it fits my body, so...
Wow, this one is cute too!
You can have as many as you want.
This cute one-piece dress is
This one over here is absolutely adorable.
I'm sure it's cute... when I wear it with this dress.
Is it okay if I try it on?
I'll try this on.
It's done! It's done!
It's so cute!
I got it.
How do you like it?
It's cute.
Good morning, ma'am.
Is it pretty?
Yay!
Yay! I got a compliment.
I got a compliment!
I'm so happy!
It's so cute!
I don't usually wear boots.
Turkish existence
Western style and Showa retro style.
I will buy this one.
I'm going to wear this for the second time.
Thank you very much.
I'm wearing a belt too, it's gonna be so cute.
I think it's done.
It's so cute.
You're wearing it more than I thought you would. What can I say?
The whole process of putting it on is so cute.
The process of buttoning and zipping it up was so cute.
I was so excited!
I'm going to buy this one.
I think this dress is absolutely adorable, too.
I want to wear it before I put it on.
Ta-da!
Thank you for your hard work!
This is cute... the belt that comes with it.
It clicks into place here.
When you put it on, it's like a little taco.
It's so cute!
The sparkles on it make it look different every time you move.
Every time you move, it shows a different expression.
It's so cute.
It makes me want to sparkle.
I've just tried on three pieces.
They are all so cute
I'm thinking of getting them all.
but I'll only be wearing one of them today.
I would like to carefully select a special dress to wear today.
I wore a cute dress like this.
Now I'd like to go to the next destination...
What a surprise!
This is it!
Right in front of the Harmony General Store!
Next, I'd like to go to Yomosugara Antique Store, which is right in front of Harmony General Store.
So close!
Dance in front of me.
Here we are!
The outside is so retro and stylish!
I'm sure there's a wonderful Showa-era retro atmosphere inside, too.
I'd like to go in.
Excuse me for interrupting, but it's nice to meet you today.
I'll leave you to it.
Wow!
It's so nice! Thank you for having me.
It's so nice here.
So many lamps!
It's as if you've wandered into a different world.
Excuse me.
Heh heh heh!
There are a lot of menus like this.
They have milkshakes!
But I guess a coffee shop should have cream sauce. It's a limited menu when the owner's here.
The omelette rice is delicious!
I'll have a curry omelet with Blue Hawaiian cream sword.
I forgot to mention that I brought my camera today.
I forgot to mention that I brought this camera today and took a lot of pictures.
Did I get it?
Camera from my point of view!
It's so cute!
Is this an accordion?
I miss accordions.
I love it.
It's fun to take a walk in retro style, isn't it?
huh?
Thank you so much!
It's so nice!
Thank you very much.
Here they are, ladies and gentlemen.
Look at all these bright colors.
Look at the shwash!
I'm so excited!
It looks delicious.
Thank you for watching.
Squishy! Delicious!
Delicious!
I'm so happy!
I want to wear it with some of the members next time.
I want to wear it with Honoka Hirao, too.
Honoka Hirao seems to fit the Showa-era retro style.
I hope we can come together in a cute dress or something.
I wish I could come and wear a cute dress with her.
Ah! Omu-rice!
Here you go.
Wow!
Curry omelet with rice!
Yes, the curry omelette is here!
Thank you very much!
It smells so good!
I wish Hario could eat it.
Hario loves omelette rice!
I'll have the omelette rice now!
Look at this!
Such a nice omelette rice!
Let's eat!
Delicious!
So delicious!
The curry is too good!
My favorite flavor!
I was on a job yesterday.
There was an omelette on site.
Hario-chan looked like she wanted to eat it so badly.
"Hal, I love omelettes.
It's so delicious!
So much so that I wanted to feed it to Haruyacha.
It's such a delicious dish!
I recently
Hina Kawada told me
She said I look like Spongy Bob the way I wash my dishes.
Really? Do I look like him?
Yes, sometimes.
Sometimes my washing style goes "wah wah wah wah".
It's like I'm washing my hair in a very friendly way on the surface.
I'm like, "Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!
Good night.
That's usually the last bite.
Thank you for the food.
It was so delicious!
So we had a delicious curry omelette rice!
It was at Yomosugara Antique Store!
We were so happy!
We were able to enjoy the Harmony General Store and the Yomosugara Antique Store
I was able to enjoy the Showa-era retro atmosphere with Harmony General Store and Yomosugara Antique Store in such close proximity!
And everyone was so kind to me, it was a very nice holiday!
So thank you again for watching today's show!
Please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
That was Hinano Uemura from Hyugaizaka 46!
Bye bye!
Hmmm...
I think I'll buy this one too.
I want a water bottle too!
Thank you.
I'll take this one too, please.
You buy too much.
I didn't think I would buy this much.
I will take good care of it and wear it a lot.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
I bought it!
Good night.